<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Conor Reynolds</title><link>https://ConorReynolds.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Conor Reynolds</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ConorReynolds.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://ConorReynolds.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 10:46:13 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://ConorReynolds.github.io/about/</guid><description>I am a PhD student at Maynooth University. My research interests include the theory of institutions, the Coq proof assistant, Event-B, and formal software design in general.
My PhD research1 involves formalising the theory of institutions in Coq, with the institution for Event-B2 as a primary use-case, supervised by Dr Rosemary Monahan. The formalisation is available on my GitHub.
Education PhD in Computer Science
Maynooth University, 2019–present MSc in Mathematics</description></item><item><title>Using Dafny to Solve the VerifyThis 2021 Challenges</title><link>https://ConorReynolds.github.io/publications/ftfjp2021/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ConorReynolds.github.io/publications/ftfjp2021/</guid><description>Abstract This paper provides an experience report of using the Dafny program verifier, at the VerifyThis 2021 program verification competition. The competition aims to evaluate the usability of logic-based program verification tools in a controlled experiment, challenging both the verification tools and the users of those tools. We present the two challenges that we tackled during the competition and discuss our solutions. As a result, we identify strengths and weaknesses of Dafny in the verification of relatively complex algorithms, and report on our experience of applying Dafny in this setting.</description></item><item><title>Formalizing the Theory of Institutions in the Coq Proof Assistant</title><link>https://ConorReynolds.github.io/publications/abz2021/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ConorReynolds.github.io/publications/abz2021/</guid><description>Abstract We formalize a fragment of the theory of institutions sufficient to establish basic facts about the institution for Event-B, and its relationship with the institution FOPEQ for first-order predicate logic. We prove the satisfaction condition for EVT and encode the institution comorphism FOPEQ → EVT embedding FOPEQ in EVT.
Funding Funded by the Irish Research Council.</description></item></channel></rss>