<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Conor Reynolds</title><link>https://ConorReynolds.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Conor Reynolds</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 15:16:57 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ConorReynolds.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About This Site</title><link>https://ConorReynolds.github.io/posts/about-this-site/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 15:16:57 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://ConorReynolds.github.io/posts/about-this-site/</guid><description>About This Site This isn&amp;rsquo;t anything like a tutorial or a comprehensive reference&amp;mdash;it&amp;rsquo;s just a dump of some of the tools, resources, and thought-processes that went into building this site, in case it would be helpful to anyone.
Fonts I went with Charter. I converted the XCharter OTF fonts to WOFF2, then base64-encoded them and baked them into my CSS. I went with XCharter rather than Bitstream Charter because it has an extended character set and more font variants&amp;mdash;including small-caps, which I use for cross-references.</description></item><item><title>What’s with the Hyperlinks?</title><link>https://ConorReynolds.github.io/posts/hyperlinks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 16:57:41 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://ConorReynolds.github.io/posts/hyperlinks/</guid><description>What&amp;rsquo;s with the Hyperlinks? Readability above all&amp;mdash;following Matthew Butterick&amp;rsquo;s example in his Practical Typography web book. One should be able to read the text from start to finish with minimal distractions. Do you know what I find distracting? Horrible blue underlined text. This is design 101: if you want people to notice something, just make it look disgusting.
Styling links in this way is common. That might be all right if your webpage is a glorified link dump (nothing wrong with that).</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://ConorReynolds.github.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ConorReynolds.github.io/contact/</guid><description>The best way to contact me is by email at conor.reynolds@mu.ie. My social links, if you can call them that, extend only as far as a GitHub account, a GitLab account, and a Twitter account&amp;mdash;created against my better judgement.</description></item><item><title>CV</title><link>https://ConorReynolds.github.io/cv/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ConorReynolds.github.io/cv/</guid><description>Still working on it! In the meantime, here&amp;rsquo;s some information of questionable note.
Education PhD in Computer Science, Maynooth University, 2019&amp;ndash;now MSc in Mathematics, Maynooth University, 2018&amp;ndash;2019 BSc in Computational Thinking, Maynooth University, 2015&amp;ndash;2018 Awards Hamilton Prize in Mathematics, awarded by the Royal Irish Academy in 2017 Turing and Cook Prizes for Computer Science, 2017 Delort Prize for Mathematics, 2016</description></item></channel></rss>